Guide to the ACTWU's Executive Vice-President's Office Records
ACTWU's Executive Vice-President's Office Records
- The Arctic Gas Project, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund. New England Plan, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  December 1
- Press Associates, Inc. Packet, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- William DuChessi. Newspaper Clippings [Folder 1 of 4], 1976-1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- William DuChessi. Newspaper Clippings [Folder 2 of 4], 1976-1978 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- William DuChessi. Newspaper Clippings [Folder 3 of 4], 1976-1978 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- William DuChessi. Newspaper Clippings [Folder 4 of 4], 1976-1978 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- William DuChessi. Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Reports. Committee on Political Education, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Summary of Labor Arbitration Awards, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous Donation Pamphlets, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- ACTWU and Willow Grove Plant Agreement, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  February 1
- The Joint Board, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  Linking the Locals
- New York State Annual Planning Report, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Knights of Vartan Convocation, Armenian Bicentennial Convocation and Annual Report of Bentley College, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Committees and Delegates List, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO Social Security Committee, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  July 18
- William DuChessi. Photographs, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Midwest Regional Conference, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  May 19-22
- COPE Operating Committee. Frontlash Subcommittee, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  August 30
- Eastern's Winter Wonderland (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Revision of Consumer Price Index and COLA Provisions in Textile Division Contracts, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Fieldcrest Mills, Inc., 1982 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Fieldcrest Wage Reopener, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Local 1855. Fieldcrest Mills, 1979-1982 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  Columbus, GA
- Fieldcrest Locals, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Synthetic Division. Gordonsville Industries, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Local 1884. Ilikon Corporation, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  Bridgeview, IL; Plant Closing
- Fieldcrest Contract Negotiation, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Removed from Gloria Shields Files April 17, 1984; Scott Hoyman's Records
- Fieldcrest Sheeting Mill, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- ACTWU Fieldcrest Wage Negotiations and Dust Proposals, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Removed from Gloria Shields Files April 17; Scott Hoyman's Records
- Scott Hoyman. Correspondence [Folder 1 of 3], 1981 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Scott Hoyman. Correspondence [Folder 2 of 3], 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Scott Hoyman. Correspondence [Folder 3 of 3], 19801-1981 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Removed from Gloria Shields Files, April 17; Scott Hoyman's Records
- Local 652. Ludlow Corporation, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  Ludlow, MA
- Company Proposals, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Local 406. Maremont Corporation, 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  Biddeford-Saco Joint Board
- Local 406. NLRB Charge, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  Maremont Corporation
- McGraw-Edison Election. Local 1016. Granite State Joint Board, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  Manchester, NJ
- Midwest Handbag Corporation. Application for Federal Fund, 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  St. Louis, MO
- Munsingwear Plant [Folder 1 of 2], 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  Fairmont, NC
- Munsingwear Plant [Folder 2 of 2], 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Munsingwear Plant. Local 1905, 1976-1979 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  Memphis, TN; From Older S. Hoyman's Files
- Munsingwear Plant. Local 1782 [Folder 1 of 2], 1969-1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  Memphis, TN; from S. Hoyman's older files
- Munsingwear Plant. Local 1782 [Folder 2 of 2], 1969-1976 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  Memphis, TN; From S. Hoyman's older files
- Munsingwear Company. Sallee and Plescia, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- National Gypsum. Coordinated Collective Bargaining, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- IUD. National Gypsum Meeting, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Niagara Hobby Distributors, Inc., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  Buffalo, NY
- Ohio City Mfg. Co., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  Ohio City, OH
- Olympia Mills, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  Plant closing 1976; Tuscaloosa, AK
- Pennsylvania Wilton Carpets, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  Philadelphia, PA
- Perfection/Eclipse Sleep Products, Inc., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  Carbon Hill, AL
- Rock-Tenn Company, 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  Phoenix City, AL
- Sanford Finishing Company, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Sealy Mattress, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Steel Pak, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  Fredericksburg, VA
- Swan Finishing Company Meeting, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  February 5
- Swan Finishing Company. Local 1483, 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  Fall River Joint Board
- Textile Examiners and Finishers, 1972-1976 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Victor-Balata Belting Company, 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  Easton, PA; Quin State
- Waverly Textile Processing, Inc., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  Plainview, NY; UTW Charge Under Article XX
- Wellman Industries, Inc. [Folder 1 of 3], 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  Johnsonville, SC
- Wellman Industries, Inc. [Folder 2 of 3], 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. [Folder 3 of 3], 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- Local 2280. Worth Textiles, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  Sylvester, GA
- CBLA Correspondence, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Negotiations [Folder 1 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Negotiations [Folder 2 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Carolina Brown Lung Association, 1974-1977 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Carolina Brown Lung Association Hearing, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  June 30
- Carolina Brown Lung Association, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Cotton Dust. Expenses, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  North Carolina Labor Law Center
- Cotton Dust. Daily News Record Articles by John Byrne, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  January 30,31 and December 1
- Brown Lung Day, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  Carolina Brown Lung Association
- OSHA Conference. Cotton Dust Manual, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- OSHA. South Carolina OSHA Plan, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- OSHA Cotton Dust Standard [Folder 1 of 2], 1976-1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- OSHA Cotton Dust Standard [Folder 2 of 2], 1976-1979 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- North Carolina Department of Labor Slide Show, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  "An Introduction to the Cotton Dust Standard"
- OSHA Slide Show on ACTWU Health and Safety Program, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- OSHA-ACTWU, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  U.S. OSHA Department: Enforcement
- OSHA. Cotton Dust Standard, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- OSHA Safety and Health, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  Textile Division
- OSHA Cotton Dust Hearing, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  Drafts of Statements, Background Data, Etc.
- ACTWU Submission to OSHA on Proposed Cotton Dust Standard, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  Volume II of Union Statement; April 5
- Cotton Dust Files, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  Statement of Sol Stetin before Subcommitee on Labor Senate Committee on Human Resources; June 30
- Toxic Chemicals Conference. G. Perkel's Paper, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- OSHA Brown Lung Week, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  October 7-14
- CLBA. United Way Controversy, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Carolina Brown Lung Association, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Brown Lung Disease. General, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- OSHA Miscellaneous Clippings and Releases, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Brown Lung Compensation Hearing, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  April 4
- Congressional Transcript of Sol Stetin's Testimony, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- OSHA J. Sheinkman's Testimony, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  April 25; Schweiker-Williams Bill
- Senator Williams OSHA Oversight Hearing, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  March 28; Schweiker-Williams Bill
- IUD AFL-CIO Schweiker-Williams Demonstration, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  Pittsburgh, PA; March 4; Schweiker-Williams Bill
- OSHA Schweiker-Williams Bill, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- NTRTP Contract, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- NTRTP General, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- NTRTP General, 1975-1979 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Emanuel Sandi, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Lou Pichinson, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Carlos Lopez, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Education Coordinator Applicants, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Camille Robinson, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Howard Brown, 19801-981 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  Appointment as Executive Director
- Applicants, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Program and NTRTP Contract, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Program Year [Folder 1 of 2], 1977-1981 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Program Year [Folder 2 of 2], 1977-1981 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- NTRTP Appeal for Extension, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Annual Board Meeting, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Joel Ronald Ax. J.P. Stevens, 1978-1980 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott. Pamphlets, Flyers and Articles [Folder 1 of 4], 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott. Pamphlets, Flyers and Articles [Folder 2 of 4], 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott. Pamphlets, Flyers and Articles [Folder 3 of 4], 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott. Pamphlets, Flyers and Articles [Folder 4 of 4], 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Status Reports. J.P. Stevens, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- J.P. Stevens. Resolutions, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- J.P. Stevens. Articles and News [Folder 2 of 2], 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- J.P. Stevens Organizing Campaign [Folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- J.P. Stevens Organizing Campaign [Folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- J.P. Stevens Testimony [Folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- J.P. Stevens. Contributions, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- J.P. Stevens. Rally, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- J.P. Stevens. Staff, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- J.P. Stevens. Legal, 1977-1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Richard Rothstein. Organizing Office, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  IUD, AFL-CIO
- J.P. Stevens. Japanese Boycott, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott [Folder 1 of 3], 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott [Folder 2 of 3], 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott [Folder 3 of 3], 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott [Folder 1 of 3], 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott [Folder 2 of 3], 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott [Folder 3 of 3], 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens Company Ad Campaign, 1977-1980 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens. Settlement Agreement Notes, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens. Settlement Agreement Clauses [Folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens. Settlement Agreement Clauses [Folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens. Contract and Company Draft [Folder 1 of 3], 1980 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens. Contract and Company Draft [Folder 2 of 3], 1980 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens. Contract and Company Draft [Folder 3 of 3], 1980 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens. Agreement with Company Drafts and Union Revisions [Folder 1 of 3], 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens. Agreement with Company Drafts and Union Revisions [Folder 2 of 3], 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens. Agreement with Company Drafts and Union Revisions [Folder 3 of 3], 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Notes on Seniority, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Hearing Officer. Local 190, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  Kenneth DeLong; Chicago, IL
- Hearing Officer. Local 658, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  Murray Moreno; Williamsport, MD
- Hearing Officer. Local 1874, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  Scott Hoyman; Cumberland, MD
- Defunct Locals Committee [Folder 1 of 2], 1965-1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Defunct Locals Committee [Folder 2 of 2], 1965-1974 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Hearing Officer. Local 1244, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  George Dillman; Phoenixville, PA
- Hearing Officer. Local 944, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  Joseph Hueter. Complaint of Peter Saia, Executive Council Meeting
- Administratorship. Local 2073, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  Philadelphia, PA; Joe Hueter, Adm.
- Hearing Officer. Local 2024, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  William Gordon; Rich Creek, VA
- Hearing Board. Greater Fall River Joint Board, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Loan Agreement Between Frank Gencarella And The Connecticut Joint Board, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Frank Gencarella. Staff Retirement [Folder 1 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Frank Gencarella. Staff Retirement [Folder 2 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- TWUA Staff Retirement Plan [Folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- TWUA Staff Retirement Plan [Folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- TWUA Staff Retirement Committee. William DuChessi, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  Staff Retirement Reports and Retirement Program Surveys
- Establishment of Joint Boards, 1980-1982 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  Upper South Regional Joint Board
- Upper South Regional Joint Board, 1980-1983 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Upper South Regional Joint Board. Personnel, 1968-1981 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Tidewater Joint Board. By-Laws, 1974-1979 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Tidewater Joint Board. Audit Reports, 1974-1981 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Upper South Tidewater Joint Board. Finances, 1977-1982 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Staff Retirement Plan. Old Correspondence [Folder 2 of 3], 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Staff Retirement Plan. Old Correspondence [Folder 3 of 3], 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Mid-Atlantic. Local 1707, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  Montgomery, PA
- Synthetics Division Meeting, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  March 28; Washington D.C.
- Synthetics Division Conference, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  March 30; Silver Spring, MD
- Mid-Atlantic Summer School, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  August 17-23; Center Valley, PA
- Synthetics Division. Organizing, 1977-1981 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Synthetics Division. Clippings, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Synthetic Apprenticeship Program. First Meeting, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Synthetics Division. Apprenticeship Training Program, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Synthetics Division Apprenticeship Program. Staff, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Synthetics Division. Bruce Dunton, 1978-1981 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Synthetics Division. Miscellaneous, 1978-1981 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Synthetics Division. The Industry, 1977-1980 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Synthetics Division. "Fiber Facts", 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  Newsletter
- Synthetics Division. Personnel, 1978-1981 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Synthetics Division. Building Lease, 1976-1978 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Synthetics Division. Worker to Worker Program, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 38)
- Labor Rally, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  Galax, VA; July 20
- Upper South Regional Director. Bruce Dunton, 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Upper South Regional Joint Board. Organizing, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  Jerry Wayne Frost Letter, July 26
- Upper South Regional Joint Board. General, 1976-1981 (Box 22, Folder 42)
- Upper South Regional Joint Board. Organizing, 1977-1981 (Box 22, Folder 43)
- Staff Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 22, Folder 44)
- ACTWU Regional Office, 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  Lynchburg, VA
- Tidewater Joint Board, 1973-1982 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  Farmville, VA
- Upper South Regional Joint Board, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Northeastern Massachusetts Joint Board, 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Staff Assignments. South General, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Mid-South Staff, 1980-1982 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Mid-South Personnel. James Renfroe, 1979-1982 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Deep South Personnel. R.L. Roper, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Mid-South Region. Staff, 1980-1982 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Deep South. Personnel, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Bi-County Join Board "Recognition Banquet", 1981 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  March 22; Reidsville, NC
- Bi-County Northern North Carolina Joint Board Conference, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  May 26-29; Blacksburg, VA
- Deep South. Central Alabama-Georgia Joint Board, 1971-1980 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Mid-South. S.C. Coastal Joint Board, 1979-1981 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Deep South. S.C. Coastal Joint Board, 1974-1976 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  South Carolina
- Deep South/Western Carolinas Joint Board. General, 1980-1982 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Local 250-T, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  Erwin, NC
- Local 254-T, 1973-1982 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Local 1093-T, 1976-1980 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  Rock Hill, SC
- Local 1355, 1977-1981 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  Fletcher, NC
- Local 1742. Jim Robbins Seat Belt Co., 1974-1979 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  Knoxville, TN
- Quin State Cincinnati Joint Board. General, 1978-1981 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Local 482-T, 1976-1981 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  Painesville, OH
- Ohio State Joint Board, 1978-1981 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Ohio State Joint Board. Legal Bills, 1975-1981 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Midwest Region. General, 1977-1981 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  Charles Sallee, Regional Director
- Chicago Joint Board Meeting and Retirement Dinner, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  January 29
- Chicago Joint Board. General, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Chicago Joint Board. General, 1979-1981 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Chicago Joint Board. Finances, 1976-1979 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Chicago Joint Board. Finances, 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Indiana-Kentucky Joint Board, 1976-1981 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- St. Louis Joint Board, 1974-1978 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Twin City Joint Board, 1976-1979 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Twin City Joint Board, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Local 194. Robert Tuckson, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Local 281, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  Bemis, TN
- Midwest Regional Conference, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  June 21-24; Springfield, IL
- Midwest Regional Staff Meeting, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  October 5; St Louis, MO
- Midwest Division. Charles Sallee, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- AFL-CIO Los Angeles-Orange Counties Organizing Committee, 1975-1981 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Portland Area Joint Board, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Los Angeles Joint Board. Subsidies, 1963-1978 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Farwest Region. Frank Nicholas, 1976-1981 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- Farwest Region. Personnel, 1973-1979 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- St. Louis Health Plan (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Farwest Region. Organizing, 1972-1979 (Box 23, Folder 47)
- Bruce Raynor. Director J.P. Stevens Advisory Council, 1981-1984 (Box 23, Folder 48)
- J.P. Stevens. Richard Rothstein, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens Advisory Council, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  Director: Richard Rothstein
- J.P. Stevens Advisory Council. Organizing, 1980-1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens Advisory Council. Personnel, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens Advisory Council, 1980-1986 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens Advisory Council. Monthly Check-Offs, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens Advisory Council. Monthly Accounting Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens Advisory Council, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- EEOC-J.P. Stevens Settlement, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- EEOC-J.P. Stevens Settlement. Background Material and Summary, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- EEOC-J.P. Stevens Settlement. EEOC Documents, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- EEOC-J.P. Stevens Settlement. Lists of Plants, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- EEOC-J.P. Stevens. Notes, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- EEOC-J.P. Stevens. Surveys and Claim Forms (Box 24, Folder 14)
- EEOC-J.P. Stevens Settlement. Press Materials and Lists, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- ITGLWF 4th World Congress. Miscellaneous Reports Prior to Congress, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- ITGLWF 4th World Congress. Meeting Notices and Schedule [Folder 1 of 2], 1984 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  October 10-26; Tel Aviv
- ITGLWF 4th World Congress. Meeting Notices and Schedule [Folder 1 of 2], 1984 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- ITGLWF 4th World Congress. Reports Received Prior to Congress [Folder 1 of 2], 1984 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- ITGLWF 4th World Congress. Reports Prior to Congress [Folder 2 of 2], 1984 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- ITGLWF 4th World Congress. ACTWU Research Department Materials, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- ILO/ITGLWF Meetings. Lists of Delegates/Files, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Calendar. Hoyman, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Third Joint Conference of Textile and Apparel Workers' Unions of Japan, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- North Carolina Council of Churches Conference, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- North Carolina State University Seminar. "Living With Your Contract", 1980 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  November 13
- Southern Staff Meeting, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  November 7
- Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- SEJ Anniversary Meeting, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  May 1, 1981; Atlanta, GA
- Leadership Seminar on Labor and the Humanities, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  September 21-23
- Scott Hoyman ACTWU Convention Speech, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  Transferred from his former office
- Scott Hoyman. Speeches, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Scott Hoyman. Speech Material, 1979-1982 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Scott Hoyman. Speech for Southern Textile Regional Joint Board, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  April 28
- Scott Hoyman. Speech for Mid-Atlantic Regional Conference, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Scott Hoyman Speech for Manhattan College. International Trade and U.S. Textile and Apparel Jobs, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  February 22; Riverdale, NY
- Scott Hoyman. Speech for ACTWU COPE Legislative Conference, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  February 24
- Scott Hoyman. Speech for ILO Textile Committee, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  October 15; Geneva, Switzerland
- Scott Hoyman. Speech for ACTWU Constitutional Convention Address, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- ACTWU 2nd Constitutional Convention. Convention Proceedings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  June 1-5; Detroit, MI
- Scott Hoyman. Personal Speech File, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- Middle Tennessee State University. Labor Management Conference, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  April 12; Murfreesboro, TN
- Scott Hoyman. Speeches, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 43)
- Botto House Dinner, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Scott Hoyman Speech. House Committee on Science and Technology, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- Upper South Regional Dinner for Sol Stetin, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  February 27
- Hoyman Trip to Egypt, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  October; In connection with ITGWLF 4th congress
- Scott Hoyman Honorary Degree. Monmouth College, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  May 18; Monmouth, IL
- Scott Hoyman Speech. Monmouth College, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  May 17; Monmouth IL
- Scott Hoyman. Revised Biographical Notes, 1983-1985 (Box 24, Folder 50)
- Scott Hoyman. Biographical Notes, 1982-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Scott Hoyman. Clippings from Newspapers Regarding, 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Scott Hoyman. "The Unsung Heroes of America's Labor Movement", 1983 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  by William Serrin, NYT
- Scott Hoyman. Labor Day Arrangements and Speech, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  Portland, ME
- Scott Hoyman. Labor Day Portland Press Herald, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  Newspaper story September 6
- Scott Hoyman. Committees and Organizations, 1983-1985 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Scott Hoyman. Invitations to ACTWU Affiliates Events, 1982-1985 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Audit of the NTRTP Program, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Audit Reports, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Contractor's Comments in Response to Draft Final Audit Report, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  June 15
- Inventory Certificates, 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- NTRTP Close Out, 1978-1983 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- NTRTP Final Inventory Certificates, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Previous Years Closeout Packages, 1978-1983 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- NTRTP Appeal, 1978-1983 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Employment Salary Records, 1976-1980 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- NTRTP Correspondence With Department of Labor, 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- National Textile Recruitment and Training Program [Folder 1 of 2], 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 18)